chienergyheals.com 2019-04-05

# School of Chi Energy Privacy Policy - School of Chi Energy

## **The School of Chi Energy Privacy Policy**

The School of Chi Energy is committed to the security of your personal information.  Please read the following carefully to understand our views and practices regarding your personal information and how we will treat it.  By submitting personal information to us, you agree to us using your data as follows.

###  **Personal Information** ** **

Our primary goal in collecting personal information is to provide you with the best and most useful content and services. One service and feature that we offer on our site require you to provide us with information as a condition of usage. These include access to a subscription-only area to access class training material (videos, audios and pdfs). “Personal information” is information that allows us to identify you.  The types of personal information that we may collect from you includes your name, email address, phone number, and account information, such as username, password.  Other information such as credit card and other payment information is directly collected by PayPal on their site. The School of Chi Energy has no access to private debit or credit card information.

###  **To Our Subscriber Free and Registered**

We may collect personal information from you, on or through the website or services in a variety of ways, including, when you: subscribe Newsletter; interact with us on social media; email, Skype and phone; details of your visits to our website, including yet not limited to cookie identifiers, traffic data, location data, communication data, whether this is required for our own site maintenance or otherwise and the resources that you access; and as a subscriber enrolled into the School of Chi Energy.  We provide a double opt out to not receive our electronic newsletters when registering. Users who opt in may remove themselves from our mailing lists at any time by clicking the “unsubscribe” link in the e-mail they received from us.

###  **Device Identifiable Information**

We may collect information that does not identify you personally, but is linked to your computer or device (“Device Identifiable Information”). We collect Device Identifiable Information from you in the normal course of operating our website. When you visit our website to browse, read or download information, we automatically collect information about your computer that your browser sends, such as your IP address, browser type and language, access times, pages visited, and referring website addresses. We may use Device Identifiable Information we collect to analyze trends, help administer the website, track the movement of visitors, to learn about and determine how much time visitors spend on each page of the website, how visitors navigate throughout the website or the Service and to gather broad demographic information for aggregate use.

We may also collect Device Identifiable Information through “cookies” or “web beacons” as explained below.

We may also collect information about your mobile device such as the type and model, operating system (e.g. iOS or Android), carrier name, mobile browser (e.g. Chrome, Safari), applications using our Website, and identifiers assigned to your device, such as its iOS Identifier for Advertising (IDFA), Android Advertising ID (AAID), or unique device identifier (a number uniquely given to your device by your device manufacturer), sometimes referred to as a mobile carrier ID.

We may also collect your location information, such as your zip code or the approximate geographic area provided by your Internet service provider (ISP) or location positioning information provided by the location services and GPS features of your mobile device when location services have been enabled.

###  **Cookies** ** **

To help us serve you better, we may collect Device Identifiable Information from you through technologies such as “cookies” or by tracking internet protocol (IP) addresses. “Cookies” are small data files that are stored by your web browser when you interact with a website. When you visit a webpage, the cookie sends back Device Identifiable Information.  Cookies operate in the background, and you can turn them off if you wish by adjusting your Web browser settings, but doing so may impair your ability to use some of the features on the website. We may use cookies to make the website work better by, for example, keeping track of your login name and password.

For more information, you may [review the FTC’s guide to opting out](https://www.consumer.ftc.gov/articles/0042-online-tracking) of online tracking for computers and mobile devices.

In some cases, we have arrangements with third-parties, such as authorized Service Providers, agents or representatives, to collect and store the foregoing information on our behalf, to provide services in connection with hosting or the operation of our website, or to facilitate reporting of analytics (such as with Google Analytics).

Although the Device Identifiable Information that we share, including the Device Identifiable Information that is not linked to your mobile device, does not identify you personally there is a risk that third parties who receive such information from us may be able to re-identify you through other information they gather.  We also may, from time to time, receive personal information about you from our third party sources to improve the website and our services, and for the various purposes outlined herein.

For the purpose of the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) and the Data Protection Act 1998 (the _Act_ ), the data controller is comprised of 3rd Parties (as shown below)  and The School of Chi Energy, LLC, of P.O. Box 2115, Apex, NC.

###  **Comments**

When visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.

An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. This is the link to the[ Gravatar service privacy policy](https://automattic.com/privacy/). After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment. ** **

###  **Where We Store Your Personal Information** ** **

The data that we collect from you may be transferred to, and stored at, a destination outside the European Economic Area (“EEA”).  By submitting your personal information, you agree to this transfer, storing or processing.  We will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure your data is treated securely and in accordance with this privacy policy. Where you have chosen a password which enables you to access certain parts of our website, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential.  We ask that you not share your password with anyone.

Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure.  Although we will do our best to secure your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of your information transmitted to our site; any transmission is at your own discretion.  Once we have received your information, we will use strict procedures and security features to prevent unauthorized access.

###  **Privacy of children**

We do not permit registration by, and will not knowingly collect or use personally identifiable information from, anyone under 18 years of age. ** **

###  **Uses of Personal Information** ** **

We may use information held about you in the following ways:

  * To send you monthly newsletters.
  * To ensure content from our website is presented in the most effective manner for you and your device that you use to access our website.
  * To provide you with information or services that you request form us.
  * To allow you to participate in interactive features of our School, when you choose to do so.
  * To notify you about changes to our School. **  
**

### **Disclosure of Personal Information** ** **

We may disclose your personal information to third parties if we are under a duty to disclose or share your personal data in order to comply with any legal obligation, or in order to enforce or apply our Terms of Use or terms and conditions of membership and other agreements; or to protect the rights, property, or safety of us or any of our customers, or others.  This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction. ** **

###  **Your Rights** ** **

Our site does contain links to and from the websites of our data controllers ( _Clicky, aMember, aWeber, HostGator_ ).  If you follow a link to any of these websites, please note that these websites have their own privacy policies and that we do not accept any responsibility or liability for these policies.  Please check these affiliate policies before you submit any personal information to these websites.

###  **Additional Information  **

Our website is operated and maintained within the United States. We make no assurances or representations of any kind that this site is suitable for use outside the United States or in the country in which you reside. The information we collect is kept on servers in the United States and may be transferred to servers in other countries, subject to the terms of this Privacy Policy. We retain the Personal Information that we collect for so long as we continue to have a business purpose for it.

By accessing this website, using a Service, establishing an account or requesting information, you consent to the processing of your Personal Information as provided in this Privacy Policy. You may withdraw that consent by contacting us at chienergyheals@gmail.com. You are required to provide certain Personal Information in order to use a Service, or to take advantage of certain features available through the website. Your failure to provide such information may preclude you from using the Services or website or may subject your account to termination, or prohibit you from using certain features.

###  **Changes to our Privacy Policy** ** **

Any changes we may make to our Privacy Policy in the future will be posted on this page and, when appropriate, emailed to you.

###  **Contact** ** **

Questions, comments, and requests regarding this Privacy Policy are welcomed and should be addressed to [chienergyheals@gmail.com](mailto:chienergyheals@gmail.com).

Last Updated: May 23, 2018
